door do do do do Jan jaan
Zen
così
Official Video Program
Jungyoo! Bad luck!
Jungyoo!Bad luck! Happiness is a star overflowing with tears and
Jungyoo! Have a place!
I can't see it, even now
Jungyoo!Bad luck!
So, today is the birthday of the 7th battle
Can I say it's at Sannyo Puroland and in the Real Birth?
Yes, that's right!
Thank you for coming today and for holding it on the same day.
Thank you very much.
Good morning and goodbye.
I wish I could say good morning and goodbye.
Let's tweak those muscles.
Let's go. Go, go, go.
I'm not going like a meathead.
Go, go, go, go.
Ready?
Cinnabar!
This girl...
Jetline.
That was a hell of an attack, jzee.
That's good.
How did you do that?
Oh, wow.
nice story bye
he looks so happy!
Oh, my gosh!
awesome!!!
BAD boring
Go.
I'm not here just to rest.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'll wrap this up now.
The more the music feels good, the better.
Beyond the last, I noticed such a scene nearby, smiling, from a kindness that I do not know.
Hai!
It's my main character.
I'm Hiraka and Nase in Asian languages. Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy for my dad. I was able to respond on the day of his birthday.
Thank you so much for coming together.
Thank you.
I am the star of the show.
Listen to it in collaboration with Cinnamon, updated on AKM2!
Today's a fairy tale. I'm crazy about it today.
Show me more! Updating!
Updating!
Cinnamon and Collaboration
Owner's announcement
Mr. Entertainment
What you can do battery
Water
A life that leaves somewhere takes with it a love
Oh my!
Hot
Please proceed to the assistance
thank you
Thank you very much.
Here we go.
Okay, okay.
It's over. It was a boy's festival.
Congratulations.
The festival.
How was your day?
Thanks to all of you.
I forgot a lot of things.
I forgot that I had to be modest
I had a lot of help and a lot of drinks, so I thought it would be nice to be pampered.
I brought you a big sleepyhead today.
You're going to say that here?
I was going to say, what time did you guys get up today?
I got up at 5:30 today.
I'm the star of the show, so I had to get up early or something.
I was so excited to get up at 5:00.
I woke up this morning and there were so many phone calls.
Then we should all go to the house right away.
I got up at 8:00.
I lied about 8:00, I got up at 7:30.
But I overslept for about two and a half hours.
It was past our meeting time.
I woke up after the meeting time.
I'm really sorry for worrying you.
I'm so grateful again that I'm standing here like this
I'm very thankful again.
I'm glad that I was able to stand up safely. I was the main character.
Too funny.
Yes, thank you very much.
I will devote myself to it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Improve, improve.
I will devote myself to it.
Thank you very much.
Improve, improve.